Oh, hey, we ran into your
mom at Benihana last night.
Uh, yeah, she loves that place.
(Howard:)Every time they flip
a shrimp in the air,
(Howard:)she practically leaps out
of her seat to catch it.
(Howard:)That's why I don't take her
to SeaWorld.
(Leonard:)I know you-you don't
want to hear it,
(Leonard:)but she was there with Stuart.
(Howard:)That's fine.
(Howard:)I don't care.
(Rajj:)It doesn't bug you when
they go out on dates?
(Howard:)They're not dating.
(Howard:)They're just two friends
who went out to dinner.
(Raj:)And then went back
to the home they share
(Raj:)where they probably fell asleep
(Raj:)in the matching pajamas
she got them
(Raj:)because they both
just love penguins.
(Howard:)Hey, lots of people
wear matching pajamas
(Howard:)who aren't dating.
(Raj:)Like who?
Like you and your dog.
(Leonard:)Don't rule out the dating.
(Howard:)Fine, it bothers me.
(Howard:)You happy?
(Sheldon:)You think you've got problems.
(Sheldon:)The gibbon is the only member
of the ape family not classified
(Sheldon:)as a great ape.
(Howard:)How is this helpful?
(Sheldon:)All the non-human apes
are classified
(Sheldon:)as great apes except one.
(Sheldon:)That means taxonomists created
the entire category
(Sheldon:)of lesser ape just
to single out the poor gibbon
(Sheldon:)as the weird kid
on the playground.
(Sheldon:)Now there's a hairy little
fellow with a genuine beef.
(Leonard:)But the gibbon doesn't know
what it's categorized as.
(Leonard:)It doesn't even know
it's called a gibbon.
(Sheldon:)True.
(Sheldon:)Sorry, kid, you've got it
worse than a gibbon.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪